Finding Aid for Detroit News records.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Detroit News records 1856-1991 1912-1982
Detroit News (Firm)
164.5 linear feet in 180 boxes
33.4 GB online
2014153 Aa 2
The Detroit News was a prominent daily newspaper founded by James Edmund Scripps in 1873. The success and expansion of the paper is largely attributed to Scripps' son-in-law, George Gough Booth. The collection contains photographic materials including glass plate negatives, film negatives, and photographic prints of various sizes as well as scrapbooks of newspaper clippings from the Detroit News.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Donated by The Detroit News (donor no. 11164 ), in September, 2014.
No further additions to the records are expected.
The collection is open for research use. Glass plate and a selection of Film negatives have been digitized and are accessible through links in this Finding Aid. Use of original materials is restricted to staff only.
The Detroit News was founded in 1873 by James Edmund Scripps (1835-1906) as an evening newspaper. By 1918, the News published a 36-page daily edition and in 1919 it absorbed the Detroit Tribune. Scripps' son-in-law, George Gough Booth (1864-1949) joined the News in 1888, and contributed to its success and expansion into a new building on Lafayette Boulevard and Fort Street in downtown Detroit. The Detroit News building was built in 1917 and designed by the architect, Albert Kahn (1869-1942). The building was designed to house all of the daily operations of the News including the printing presses required to print the newspaper. The building also had its own hospital, library, barber shop and auto repair shop. The Detroit News' radio station, WWJ was founded in 1920 and is one of America's oldest operating radio broadcasting stations. WWJ's high frequency transmitter, W8XWJ, allowed the Detroit News to become the first newspaper to use an airplane to cover and report the news in 1931. In 1960, the News purchased and closed the Detroit Times and in 1989 entered into a joint operating agreement with the Detroit Free Press.
The collection includes two primary series: Visual Materials and Scrapbooks.
The Detroit News records, 1856-1991 (164.5 linear feet) consist of photographic materials including glass plate negatives, film negatives, and photographic prints of various sizes as well as scrapbooks containing newspaper clippings from the Detroit News. The arrangement of the collection is alphabetical and maintains original order as far as could be discerned. In instances where multiple formats were stored together, they have been rehoused separately for preservation purposes. Researchers are encouraged to review the entire container list of this finding aid to identify corresponding materials of different formats within the collection, which have been indicated.
The researcher will find that a significant portion of the photographic materials depict interior and exterior views of the Detroit News building designed by Albert Kahn and erected in 1917. Additional topics of photographic materials include the radio station, WWJ and various events hosted by the News. Images of the Scripps and Booth families as well as employees of the Detroit News are also present among the collection. The scrapbooks contain newspaper clippings, which present a broad range of subject matter as covered by a daily metropolitan newspaper. All of the glass plate negatives and a selection of film negatives have been digitized and can be viewed by following the links in the container list of this finding aid.
Subjects:
Booth, George G. (George Gough), 1864-1949.; Buildings--Michigan--Detroit.; Cobb, Ty, 1886-1961.; Couzens, James, 1872-1936.; Cranbrook Press.; Detroit News (Firm); Detroit (Mich.); Detroit (Mich.)--Politics and government--20th century.; Detroit Tigers (Baseball team); Ford Motor Company.; Kahn, Albert, 1869-1942.; Prohibition.; Romney, George W., 1907-1995.; Scripps, James E. (James Edmund), 1835-1906.; Spelling bees--Michigan--Detroit.; United States--Politics and government--20th century.; Williams, G. Mennen, 1911-1988.; Yost, Fielding Harris, 1871-1946.; Young, Coleman A., 1918-1997.
Subjects - Visual Materials:
Labor unions--Michigan--Detroit.; Newspaper carriers--Michigan--Detroit.; Printing presses--Michigan--Detroit.; Radio stations--Michigan--Detroit.; School children--Michigan--Detroit.; Streets--Michigan--Detroit.
Genre Terms:
Acetate film.; Cellulose nitrate film.; Digital file formats.; Glass plate negatives.; Scrapbooks.; Transparencies.
- Visual Materials
  The Visual Materials series (1906-1984, 10 linear feet, 33.4 GB) has been divided into two subseries, Negatives and Photographic Prints.
  - Negatives
    The Negatives subseries (1906-1984, 9.75 linear feet) contains glass plate and film negatives as well as positive glass transparencies. These materials have been arranged further within the Negatives subseries by format, Glass Plate and Film. These materials range in size from 4 x 5 inches to 11 x 14 inches and are arranged alphabetically by folder headings, which were maintained from their original folders. Film negatives, 1922-1984 (2.75 linear feet) range in size from 4 x 5 inches to 8 x 10 inches and are comprised of both acetate and nitrate film. Content of the film negatives includes images of classroom scenes, crowds in the streets after a Joe Louis victory, a civil rights picket line outside of Woolworth's, and WWJ entertainers in costume. Glass negatives, 1906-1936 (7 linear feet) range in size from 4 x 5 inches to 11 x 14 inches. Content of the glass negatives is less varied than that of the film negatives and includes large runs of images depicting interior and exterior views of the Detroit News building and the previous News building on Shelby Street and Larned Street in downtown Detroit, as well as of the WWJ radio station building. Some of the smaller glass negatives include more editorial content such as images of the annual spelling bee and the Detroit News 50th Anniversary hosted at the Scripps family farm.
    - Film negatives
      - Bread Contest, undated
      - Building Excavation for New Press Room-Exterior Views of Finished Structure, 1929, 2 negatives
      - Craftsmanship-Toys, 1935, 5 negatives
      - Employees-Hiking Executives, 1936
      - Employees-Photographic-Christmas Card, 1944
      - Experience Column-Carillon, 1939, 3 negatives
      - Fair and Square Club-Trophy, 1934-1935, 4 negatives
      - Green, Jerry (Jerome)-Detroit News Emp. Editorial-Sports, 1966-1984, 17 negatives
      - Halloween Scenes-Ann Seiter as a Witch, 1958, 2 negatives
      - Hikers-Hiking Club, 1940
      - Jackson-Silver Dome, 1984
      - Medal of Valour for Police, 1928, 2 negatives
      - Negroes-Detroit, 1935-1962
      - New Building-Interior-Reference Department-Recordak Projector, 1938
      - Radio-Entertainers-"Frank & Ernst"-Arnold Tieman, Frank Greenwood, 1935
      - Radio-Equipment-Ultra High Frequency Converter Designed and Built by A. B. Allen 1936, 2 negatives
      - Radio-History-First Local Candidate to Speak Over WWJ-Charles L. Bowles, Recall Campaign, 1930
      - Radio-Microphone, 1932-1937, 9 negatives
      - Radio-Mobile Unit #1-Pack Set-Equipment, 1937, 7 negatives
      - Radio-Players-Bloomer Girls, 1931
      - Radio-Programs-"Smoothies"-Gail Abbey, Jack Hill, Georgia Leath, Bobette Hall, 1935, 5 negatives
      - Radio-Short Wave Adapter-Equipment, 1935-1936, 2 negatives
      - Radio-Short Wave Station-Antenna on Penobscot Building Tower 1946
        [see also: glass plate negatives]
      - Radio-Staff-Elwood Ryan, Kurt Schmeissen, Louis Cohen, and Lillian Dixon 1937, 2 negatives
      - Radio-Studio-New-Exterior View-Night Scene-Crowd Leaving 16th Birthday Party
      - Radio-Towers-Birds on Tower, 1934
      - Schools-Classroom Scenes, 1938-1959, 9 negatives
      - Schools-Classroom Scenes-Doty School, Monteith School, Hubert School, 1934-1958, 5 negatives
        [see also: glass negatives]
      - Scotten-Dillon Tobacco Company-Detroit, 1965
      - Spelling Bee-Contestants, 1933-1934, 2 negatives
      - Spelling Bee-Medal, undated
      - Spelling Contest-Champion, Dorothy Karrick, 1925
        [see also: box 4]
      - Television-Equipment-Antenna on Penobscot Building, 1949-1950, 6 negatives
      - Television-Tower-Construction, 1954, 10 negatives
      - Travel Show-Crowds, 1950, 2 negatives
      - Warehouse-Lombardo 10/18/1949-Roto 11/20/1949-Photos from Bridge, 1949, 6 negatives
      - Advertising-Detroit News Lettering on Downtown Detroit, 1932, 5 negatives
      - Advertising-Detroit News Sign, 1932, 6 negatives
      - Advertising-Law Suit vs. "The Colonial Hotel", 1931
      - Branches-Downtown Office (Majestic Building), 1923-1930
      - Branch Offices-General Motors Building, 1929, 3 negatives
      - Bread Contest, 1922, 7 negatives
      - Building-Architect's Drawings for Enlargement, 1930
      - Carriers, 1929, 20 negatives
      - Carriers on Steps in Front of United Nations Building in New York, 1954
      - Chorus, 1928, 3 negatives
      - Circulation Department Staff, 1930, 2 negatives
      - Cooking School-Crowd-Auditorium, 1932, 4 negatives
      - Cooking School-Crowd in Auditorium, 1933, 2 negatives
      - Cooking School-Crowd at Entrance-Masonic Temple, 1931
      - Cooking School-Held at Masonic Temple Auditorium, 1928
      - Craftsmanship-Interior View of Workshop, 1935, 11 negatives
      - Delivery Services-Trucks, 1929, 6 negatives
      - Dock, Detroit River, between 1st & 2nd Avenues, 1926, 4 negatives
      - Employees-Department Heads, 1938, 5 negatives
      - Employees-Dinner for "Key Men", 1939, 2 negatives
      - Experience Column-Sunrise Service at Belle Isle, 1934
      - New Building-Exterior-Lafayette Entrance View Taken from Second and Lafayette, 1928-1933, 5 negatives (Box 2)
      - New Building-Exterior-Radio Tower, 1932, 2 negatives (Box 2)
      - New Building-Exterior-Sketch of Proposed Addition, 1927 (Box 2)
      - New Building-Exterior-Views Showing News, 1926-1940, 10 negatives (Box 2)
      - New Building-Exterior-Views of Side Facing Fort Street, undated, 3 negatives (Box 2)
      - New Building-Exterior-Warehouse, 1931, 3 negatives (Box 2)
      - New Building-Interior-Art Department-New Addition, 1940, 2 negatives (Box 2)
      - New Building-Interior-Art Room-Fourth Floor, 1933 (Box 2)
      - New Building-Interior-Advertising Room, 1931-1935, 7 negatives (Box 2)
      - New Building-Interior-Nancy Brown's Office-Fourth Floor, 1939, 2 negatives (Box 2)
      - New Building-Interior-Business Office-Mr. Montgomery's Office, 1924 (Box 2)
      - New Building-Interior-Composing Room, 1931-1938, 6 negatives (Box 2)
      - New Building-Interior-Conference Room-Clubwomen Being Entertained by Mrs. Smith, Mary Morris, Ethel Ehlen, Mrs. Chittenden, and Jacqueline Frost, 1934 (Box 2)
      - New Building-Interior-Editorial Reception Room, undated (Box 2)
      - New Building-Interior-Editorial Room, 1931 (Box 2)
      - New Building-Interior-Hospital, 1933 (Box 2)
      - New Building-Interior-Library, 1931, 2 negatives (Box 2)
      - New Building-Interior-Mailing Room, 1923, 9 negatives (Box 2)
      - New Building-Interior-Photographers' Studio, 1929, 5 negatives (Box 2)
      - New Building-Interior Views-Photographer's Studio, 1933, 4 negatives (Box 2)
      - New Building-Interior-Photographic Department, 1931-1939, 24 negatives (Box 2)
      - New Building-Interior-Press Room-Showing Roto Presses, 1932, 7 negatives (Box 2)
      - New Building-Interior-Press Room-Views of Presses and Pressmen, 1927-1938, 30 negatives (Box 2)
      - New Building-Interior-Press Room, Electrical Controls, Board for Presses, undated, 4 negatives (Box 2)
      - New Building-Interior-Reference Department, 1930-1939, 10 negatives (Box 2)
      - New Building-Interior-Stereotype Room, 1938, 2 negatives (Box 2)
      - New Building-Interior-Storage Room for Paper, undated (Box 2)
      - New Building-Interior-Switchboard, undated (Box 2)
      - New Building-Interior-View of Sub Basement Showing A.C. Switchboard, 1932 (Box 2)
      - New Building-Interior-"Women's Department"-First Floor, 1928-1934, 3 negatives (Box 2)
      - Old Building-Interior-Cranbrook Press-Owned by George Gough Booth, undated, 2 negatives (Box 2)
      - Old Building-Interior-Editorial, 1931
      - Photo Show-Cedar Pointe, 1931, 4 negatives
      - Photo Show-General Motors Building, 1931, 28 negatives
      - Radio-Awards, 1950
      - Radio-Birthday Party-10th Anniversary, 1930, 5 negatives
      - Radio-Birthday Party-12th Anniversary, 1932
      - Radio-Birthday Party-15th Anniversary-Showing First Transmitter Ever Used, 1935
      - Radio-Birthday Party-16th Anniversary-In New WWJ Studio, 1936
      - Radio-Entertainers-Detroit News Hour, 1932
      - Radio-Entertainers-Frank and Ernest, 1931, 3 negatives
      - Radio-Entertainers-Wynn Wright Reading Comics, 1932
      - Radio-Miscellaneous-David J. Wilkie and His Bulletins, 1931
      - Radio-Orchestra, 1930-1933, 10 negatives
      - Radio-Orchestra, 1932, 5 negatives
      - Radio-Orchestra-Showing Control Room, 1933
      - Radio-Orchestra and String Quartet, undated, 7 negatives
      - Radio-Organ-Ole Foerch Playing, 1931
      - Radio-Players-Rita Alcock and William Morrison, 1933, 2 negatives
      - Radio-Players-Cadillac-Herbert Labadie, 1931, 3 negatives
      - Radio-Players-Plays, 1931, 8 negatives
      - Radio-Players-Lew Weitzman and Jade Leland, 1933
      - Radio-Players-Dr. B.D. Welling and Glendora Forshee, 1933, 2 negatives
      - Radio-Plays-"Dr. Grimm" Cast, 1934
      - Radio-Programs-Old Detroiter and Bobby, 1932
      - Radio-Short Wave-W8XWJ-Lobby, 1938-1940, 2 negatives (Box 3)
      - Radio-Short Wave Station-W8XWJ-Equipment in Penobscot Building, 1936-1938, 11 negatives (Box 3)
      - Radio-Staff, undated (Box 3)
      - Radio-Studio-New-Construction-Series "B", 1936, 8 negatives (Box 3)
      - Radio-Studio-New-Construction-Series "C", 1936, 8 negatives (Box 3)
      - Radio-Studio-New-Construction-Series "E", 1936, 9 negatives (Box 3)
      - Radio-Studio-New-Construction-Series "F", 1936, 2 negatives (Box 3)
      - Radio-Studio-New-Construction-Identification for Series A, B, C, D, E, and F, 1936 (Box 3)
      - Radio-Studio-New-Equipment, 1936, 4 negatives (Box 3)
      - Radio-Studio-New-Exterior View, 1936-1941, 12 negatives (Box 3)
      - Radio-Studio-New-Exterior View-Night Scene, 1936 (Box 3)
      - Radio-Studio-New-Exterior-Sculpture on East and West Side of Entrance, 1936, 2 negatives (Box 3)
      - Radio-Studio-New-Interior-Air Conditioning System, 1936, 2 negatives (Box 3)
      - Radio-Studio-New-Interior-Audition Room, 1936 (Box 3)
      - Radio-Studio-New-Interior-Auditorium Studio and Orchestra, 1936-1939, 5 negatives (Box 3)
      - Radio-Studio-New-Interior-Client's Room, 1936 (Box 3)
      - Radio-Studio-New-Interior-Control Room, 1936, 2 negatives (Box 3)
      - Radio-Studio-New-Interior-Lobby-Main Lobby, 1936, 2 negatives (Box 3)
      - Radio-Studio-New-Interior-Manager's Office, 1936 (Box 3)
      - Radio-Studio-New-Interior-News Room, 1938, 2 negatives (Box 3)
      - Radio-Studio-New-Interior-Reception Desk-3rd Floor, 1936 (Box 3)
      - Radio-Studio-New-Interior-Sales Manager's Office, 1936 (Box 3)
      - Radio-Studio-New-Interior-Studios A, B, C, and D, 1936, 10 negatives (Box 3)
      - Radio-Studio-Old-Equipment, 1922-1931, 19 negatives (Box 3)
      - Radio-Studio-Old-Equipment-Transmitter and Control Room, 1921-1930, 15 negatives (Box 3)
      - Radio-Studio-Old-Interior-Studios A, B, and C, 1930 (Box 3)
      - Radio-Subway, 1936 (Box 3)
      - Radio-Tower-New-On New Transmitting Station, Meyers and Eight Mile Road, 1935, 8 negatives (Box 3)
      - Radio-Towers-Old, 1934 (Box 3)
      - Radio-Transmitter-New-Building-Exterior, 1936-1941, 14 negatives (Box 3)
      - Radio-Transmitter-New-Diagram, 1936 (Box 3)
      - Radio-Transmitter-New-Equipment-Display Window-Rectifier Tube Rack, 1936 (Box 3)
      - Radio-Transmitter-New-Equipment-Rectifier, 1936 (Box 3)
      - Radio-Transmitter-New-Equipment-Scripps Motor, 1937, 2 negatives (Box 3)
      - Radio-Transmitter-New-Equipment-Transformers, 1936 (Box 3)
      - Radio-Transmitter-New-Garage, 1936 (Box 3)
      - Radio-Transmitter-New-Interior-Control Room, 1936, 3 negatives (Box 4)
      - Radio-Transmitter-New-Interior-Caretaker's Apartment, 1936, 5 negatives (Box 4)
      - Radio-Transmitter-New-Interior-Carpenter Shop, 1936 (Box 4)
      - Radio-Transmitter-New-Interior-Control Room, 1936, 3 negatives (Box 4)
      - Radio-Transmitter-New-Interior-Fuse Room, 1936 (Box 4)
      - Radio-Transmitter-New-Interior-Hall and Staircase-New Transmitting Station, 1936, 2 negatives (Box 4)
      - Radio-Transmitter-New-Interior-Lobby-Showing Mural, 1936, 2 negatives (Box 4)
      - Radio-Transmitter-New-Interior-Murals, 1936, 3 negatives (Box 4)
      - Radio-Transmitter-New-Interior-Office, 1936 (Box 4)
      - Radio-Transmitter-New-Interior-Operators Bunks, 1936, 2 negatives (Box 4)
      - Radio-Transmitter-New Building-Exterior, 1937 (Box 4)
      - Rotogravure Sections-Retouching, 1929, 2 negatives
      - Spelling Bee, 1929, 3 negatives
      - Spelling Bee-Coliseum Scenes, 1930, 6 negatives
      - Spelling Bee-Coliseum Scenes, 1932, 5 negatives (Box 4)
      - Spelling Bee-Coliseum Scenes, 1933, 3 negatives (Box 4)
      - Spelling Bee-Coliseum Scenes, 1934 (Box 4)
      - Spelling Bee-Coliseum Scenes, 1936 (Box 4)
      - Spelling Bee-Coliseum Scenes, 1937, 5 negatives (Box 4)
      - Spelling Bee-Coliseum Scenes, 1938, 2 negatives (Box 4)
      - Spelling Bee-Group Photo of Contestants, 1930, 2 negatives
      - Spelling Bee-Group Photo of Contestants, 1932, 2 negatives
      - Spelling Bee-Medal, 1929
      - Spelling Contest, 1927, 4 negatives
      - Spelling Contest, 1928, 3 negatives
      - Spelling Contest-Vivian Bremer-Winner, 1926, 4 negatives
      - Spelling Contest-Dorothy Karrick-Winner, 1925, 9 negatives
        [see also: box 1]
      - Spelling Contest-Justine Pearsall-Winner, 1922, 16 negatives
      - Young Writers' Club, 1928, 7 negatives
    - Glass Plate Negatives
      - Armour, William-Former Manager of Tigers Baseball Team
      - Armour, William-Former Manager of Tigers Baseball Team
      - Armour, William-Former Manager of Tigers Baseball Team
      - Barbecue-Parade, undated, 4 negatives
      - Barbecue-Mr. George Booth with: Mr. Scott, Mr. George Miller, Mr. M. Bingay, Mr. William Scripps. Mr. Scripps also with Wife and Mother, 1923, 3 negatives
      - Barbecue-Trip to Grove for Lunch, Meat Roasting Spits, Guests as Tables, Spectators Watching Games-50th Anniversary at Scripps Farm, undated, 2 negatives
      - Bread Contest, undated
      - Building Excavation for New Press Room, undated, 2 negatives
      - Detroit Riding and Hunt Club-Horses in Paddock, undated, 2 negatives
      - Dock, Detroit River, between First and Second Avenues, 1926, 2 negatives
      - Fish Sale, undated, 2 negatives
      - Model House-Exterior View, undated
      - Parades-Beer Parade, 1932, 3 negatives
      - Radio-Short Wave Station-Antenna on Penobscot Building Tower, 1936, 2 negatives
      - Radio-Towers-Birds on Tower, 1933, 2 negatives
      - Rolls of Paper Unloaded from Truck in Warehouse, undated, 2 negatives
      - Schools-Classroom Scenes-Doty School, Monteith School, Hubert School, 1935
        [see also: film negatives]
      - Spelling Contest-Champion, Vivian Braemer, 1926
      - Spelling Contest-Champion, Hilda Fornell, 1927
      - Cigar Factory-Women Making Cigars, undated, 2 negatives
      - Detroit News-Employees-And Views of Old and New Buildings, undated
      - Fish Campaign, undated, 7 negatives
      - Building-Architect's Drawings for Enlargement, 1930
      - New Building-Construction, 1915-1916, 8 negatives
      - New Building-Excavation, 1915, 1 negatives
        (1 of 7 negatives)
      - New Building-Excavation, 1915, 6 negatives
        (2-7 of 7 negatives)
      - New Building-Exterior
      - New Building-Exterior-Decorated for 32nd Division Reunion, undated, 5 negatives
      - New Building-Exterior-Lafayette Entrance View Taken from Second and Lafayette, undated, 4 negatives
      - New Building-Lafayette Side-View Taken from Third Street, 1917
      - New Building-Exterior-Views of Courtyard, undated
      - New Building-Exterior-Views of Side Facing Fort Street, undated, 2 negatives
        [1-2 of 6 negatives; see also: film negatives]
      - New Building-Exterior-Views of Side Facing Fort Street, undated, 4 negatives
        [3-6 of 6 negatives; see also: film negatives]
      - New Building-Interior-Art Room (Former One on Third Floor)-Mural Decorations, undated, 6 negatives
      - New Building-Interior-Composing Room, undated, 2 negatives
      - New Building-Interior-Dark Room, undated, 7 negatives
      - New Building-Interior-Editorial Room, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Hospital, undated
      - New Building-Interior-Lobby-Second Floor, undated, 3 negatives
      - New Building-Interior-Mailing Room, undated, 5 negatives
      - New Building-Interior-Press Room-New Presses, undated, 4 negatives
      - New Building-Interior-Stereotype Room, undated, 2 negatives
      - New Building-Interior-Storage Room for Paper, undated, 3 negatives
      - Old Building-Exterior-Delivery Trucks Lined up Outside Old Building, 1912, 2 negatives
      - Old Building-Exterior-Views of Building on Shelby and Larned, undated, 2 negatives
      - Old Building-Interior-Advertising Department-Business Office, undated, 3 negatives
      - Old Building-Interior-Art Room, 1912, 2 negatives
      - Old Building-Interior-Composing Room-Stereotype Room, 1912, 9 negatives
      - Old Building-Interior-Fairwell Night, 1917
      - Old Building-Interior-Paper Storage Room, 1910
      - Old Building-Interior-Photographers' Room, undated, 2 negatives
      - Old Building-Interior-Press Room, 1910-1912, 3 negatives
      - Old Building-Interior-Sunday News Room Magazine, 1906
      - Radio-Studio-Old-Equipment, undated
      - Radio-Studio-Old-Equipment-Transmitter and Control Room-Radio History-First Broadcast from a Commercial Station-Early WWJ, 1921
      - Tribune-Group Portrait of Tribune Staff-When Paper was Discontinued, undated
      - Young Writers' Club, undated, 2 negatives
      - Art Department, undated
      - Art Department-Kraemer's Corner, undated, 2 negatives
        [see also: photographic print]
      - Automatic Telephone, undated
        [see also: photographic prints]
      - Bindery, undated, 2 negatives
      - Bingay's Office, undated
      - Building Exterior, undated, 2 negatives
      - Business Office, 1907
      - Business Office, 1912
      - Business Office, 1912
      - Business Office, undated
      - Business Office, undated
      - Carriers-Horse Drawn-Building at Corner of Larned and Shelby Streets-Some of Delivery Service Crew, circa 1904
      - City Room, 1907
      - City Room, 1912
      - City Room, undated
      - City Room, undated
      - Composing Room, 1912
      - Composing Room, undated
      - Critics, undated
      - Engraving Department-Etching, undated
      - Engraving Department-Hand Proof Press, undated
      - Garage, undated
      - Garage Repair Shop, undated
      - Hospital, undated, 2 negatives
      - Ink Tanks, undated
      - Ink Tank Truck, undated, 2 negatives
      - Ink Tank Truck, undated
      - Library-Bound Files, undated
      - Library-New Building, undated, 2 negatives
        (1-2 of 3 negatives)
      - Library-New Building, undated, 1 negatives
        (3 of 3 negatives)
      - Lobby-3rd Floor-New Building, circa 1917
      - Mailing Room, 1912
      - Mailing Room, 1912